question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In ;Space Station 13;,  the station has a clown aboard it.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the ;Dragon Slayer; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
     "question": "Adolf Hitler was tried at the Nuremberg trials.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Celebrities",
     "question": "Marilyn Monroe was born on July 1, 1926.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Nintendo&#039;s Luigi was originally just called Green Mario?",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "Pointers were not used in the original C programming language; they were added later on in C++.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "A flock of crows is known as a homicide.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The name of the main character of the video game The Legend of Zelda, is Zelda.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
